the shoeshine stand at the airport the
guy goes here man your shoes your shoes
look bad hop up or I'll fix you up okay
my shoes look bad but it's that really
an acceptable a to drum up business by
insulting me I've never walked in front
of a clothing store I have the guy
stealing them out front going get your
raggedy butt in here you got to be
ashamed of yourself walking around town
looking like that comb your hair you bum
how's that the Mali idea saw a store a
shoe store had a big sign up that said
semiannual fall sale fall comes once a
year according to my calendar I bought a
pair of sneakers I think I get a good
price
I put $50 down and I'm paying five
dollars a month for 60 months that's
where they get you you ever got a
payless Shoe Store pay less they're all
right right okay if you go in the
morning when it's still sort of
organized you know what I mean you go
later in the day it looks like it looks
like the three stooges that a shoe fight
in their lids and boxes all over the
place I've been for like foot lock we
got a point to the shoe up on the wall
to the guy yeah hey I like this shoe
here do you think you just go to
backroom and screw around about 20
minutes playing video games or whatever
the heck it is you do back there how big
is that warehouse back behind that door
like he's getting on the forklift in
driving for miles
this is looking for my sneakers
last time the guy comes out and he comes
out to me he's got two boxes he said
I'll have a still have a size 10 but I
have an eight-and-a-half and an 11
really well I'm pretty sure you ain't a
half's will hurt my feet yeah cuz last
time I got eight and a half's both my
feet hurt constantly but maybe I get the
Elevens and stuff newspapers up into the
toes maybe gonna buy those tube socks
over there they say the fit sizes 6
through 12
and just flap unused portion underneath
my foot would that be a recommendation
mr. referee just called a whistle twice
if the answer is yes
six wildest Oxman Shaquille O'Neal and I
were the same sax
I was looking at a pair of shoes in the
shoe store on the Avenue this pair of
shoes was secluded from the other shoes
understand something like this right
and I'm just looking at them trying to
figure out why they're all separated and
the guy comes up says that's a great
shoe that was the first shoe ever
designed specifically for walking right
there as if the sandals Moses what we
designed for racquetball Galileo he wore
cross trainers all around town I asked
the guy said heels belts in that are
designed to hold up your pants and they
invented that yes sir
I bought belt the other day I bought a
reversible belt when I was a kid my dad
had a reverse we'll go
I remember one side was brown and the
other side was a whip yeah I remember I
remember
I like brown I like brown that was my
preference
I thought he looked good in brown a lot
of young guys these days we're not
wearing any belts at all right you've
seen I'm gonna have the pants hanging
down low so everybody can see they're
under way it's supposed to be sexy
that's what I've been told and I agree
but you know what I like to do sometimes
like I like to put my pants on first
then I put my underwear up over my pants
then I pulled my underwear down a little
bit in the back and give people a peek
at my pants I think I think that's sexy
I think that sexy
you know I also like where I like to
wear both of my shoes on the same foot
I think that's sexy I can pull it off
comes in eight and a half one is it 11
I like the gap like shopping at the gap
one reason I'm still at 34 waist at the
gap
yeah not everywhere but the gap was a 30
for regular fit for a long time that was
the 34 relaxed fit for a while that was
a 34 easy fit now I'm a 34 loose fit but
I'm still a 34 got a bite size 40
underwear for some reason set a
different system altogether get the 34
Sun this is all wrong it's like a
tourniquet subscribe to drive our comedy
for even more of the world's largest
collection of clean comedy